http://www.urenco.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy | Urenco
Do you consent to this website placing cookies on your device? You can find out more by reading our cookies policy.
50 Years
This year, we're celebrating the 50th anniversary of our founding treaty, the Treaty of Almelo.
Urenco ChemPlants
Urenco ChemPlants owns and will operate our most recent nuclear new build, Urenco’s Tails Management Facility.
Richie Education Programme
One of our long standing sustainability commitments is to nurture the next generation of scientists and engineers.
Half Year 2020 Unaudited Financial Results
We announced our results for the half year ended 30 June 2020 on 6 August 2020.
Code of Conduct
Urenco UK Pension Scheme - Statement of Investment Principles and Annual Report 2019
Gender Pay Gap Report
Diversity and inclusion is a high priority as we want to create a workforce that reflects the society in which we operate.
Privacy Policy
We comply with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and for the purposes of this regulation the data controller is Urenco Limited (Registered Office: Urenco Court, Sefton Park, Bells Hill, Stoke Poges, Buckinghamshire, SL2 4JS, Company Number: 01022789).
Urenco Limited is under a legal duty to protect any personal information we collect and will only use that information in accordance with the law, including the GDPR. We use appropriate technologies and encryption to safeguard data and apply strict security standards to prevent any unauthorised access to it.
This privacy policy will inform you as to how we look after your personal data when you visit our website and tell you about your privacy rights and how the law protects you.
What information do we collect from visitors to our website?
With regard to each of your visits to our site we may automatically collect the following user data, for the following purposes:
Technical information (such as the IP address and browser type).
Information about your visit (such as the pages you request, clickstream to, through and from our site, download errors and page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks and mouse overs)).
Small bits of data stored on your computer called ‘cookies’. Find out what we use them for, and how you can control their use by viewing our cookie policy.
This data is processed in a way that does not identify individuals. We do not make any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our website. We will use this data to administer and improve our site and for internal operations, including data analysis, testing and statistical purposes.
What happens when you link to another site?
The Urenco Limited website contains links to other Urenco company websites.
The Urenco Limited website may also include links to third party websites, plugins and applications. It is important that you read the privacy statement of any website which collects personal information. We do not control these third party websites and are not responsible for their privacy policy.
We do not pass on any personal information you have given us to any third parties.
Use of your information
This is information about you that you provide us when corresponding with us by phone, email or otherwise. The information you give us may include your name, address, email address and phone number and, should you wish to physically visit one of our facilities, appropriate photo ID. We will use this to provide you with the information that you request from us, organise further contact, and to ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.
Log files
We use our website server log file to identify patterns of website use to enable us to improve the service we offer our site visitors. We do not use them to identify individual users of our website.
Disclosure of your information
We will have the right to share your personal information with third parties where:
You have applied for employment, selected third parties that assist us with our recruitment process.
We are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms and conditions.
Security
We will ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy and GDPR requirements, and we will store your personal data for no longer than is necessary for the purposes for which the personal data is processed.
Your legal rights
You have the right to:
Request access to your personal data (commonly known as a data subject access request).
Request correction of the personal data that we hold about you.
Request erasure of your personal data.
Object to processing of your personal data where we are relying on legitimate interest and there is something which makes you feel that the processing of your data impacts on your fundamental rights and freedoms.
Request restriction of processing of your personal data.
Withdraw consent at any time where we are relying on consent to process your personal data.
If you wish to exercise any of your above rights please contact Urenco Limited’s representative by writing to the following address or email:
Head of Group Internal Audit and Risk, Urenco Court, Sefton Park, Bells Hill, Stoke Poges, SL2 4JS.
privacy@urenco.com.
You also have the right to lodge a complaint with the relevant data protection authority if you believe that we have not complied with applicable data protection laws. For the UK, this would be the Information Commissioner’s Office (www.ico.org.uk). A list of authorities for all countries in the European Economic Area is available from the European Commission (www.ec.europa.eu).
This privacy policy forms part of the terms and conditions for our site and should be read in conjunction with the website terms and conditions and terms of use.
Newsletter
Sign up to our newsletter by entering your email address below.
Email Address
Please tick to confirm that you consent to us processing your information for purposes relating to your enquiry. Our privacy
notice is available here which includes details on how you can withdraw consent at any time.
© 2020 Urenco. All rights reserved.
